{"1": {"question": "What is the art song set work?", "correct": "O Mistress Mine from Let Us Garlands Bring Op.18 ", "incorrect": ["O Mistress Mine from Garlands Let Us Take Op.81 ", "Airplane, Pt.2 by BTS (highly recommend)", "O Mistress Mine from Let Us Bring Garlands Op.28 "]}, "2": {"question": "Who wrote the text of Let Us Garlands Bring?", "correct": "Shakespeare", "incorrect": ["Hitman Bang", "Milton", "Coleridge"]}, "3": {"question": "How many separate texts does Let Us Garlands Bring set?", "correct": "Five", "incorrect": ["Thirteen", "Eight", "Eleven"]}, "4": {"question": "Which of the following was NOT a composer of art song?", "correct": "[lieder composer]", "incorrect": ["Ralph Vaughan Williams", "John Ireland", "Arnold Bax"]}, "5": {"question": "What is O Mistress Mine about?", "correct": "It is a light-hearted reflection on love and youth.", "incorrect": ["It is a deep reflection on love and the mortality of youth.", "It is a light-hearted reflection on being grateful for little things.", "It is about waiting for 00:00 when the day will be over"]}, "6": {"question": "What was the 'English musical Renaissance'?", "correct": "The period in which England freed themselves from foreign musical influences, to have begun writing in a distinctively national manner", "incorrect": ["The period in which England freed themselves from old national English music and changed their style.", "The period in which English composers competed against BTS as to who could write better songs, and BTS won.", "The period in which England was overwhelmed by foreign musical influences and lost their national musical style."]}, "7": {"question": "Who wrote the art song set work?", "correct": "Gerald Finzi", "incorrect": ["Franz Schubert", "George Friedric Handel", "Rapmon"]}, "8": {"question": "What is the rhyme scheme of each sextain in Let Us Garlands Bring?", "correct": "AABCCB", "incorrect": ["ABACDC", "AAABBB", "ABBCBB"]}, "9": {"question": "Finzi - How are the modulations in the piece used to reflect the ideas in the text?", "correct": "The piece is bouncy as the poet addresses the object of his affection, and becomes more reflective as the poet addresses the need to be joyful while still young.", "incorrect": ["The song is determined as the idea of surviving one more day is expressed, and is temporarily taken back a notch as though building up energy to explode. ", "The piece is more reflective as the poet addresses the object of his affection, and becomes bouncy as the poet addresses the need to be joyful while still young.", "The piece is slow and melancholy as the poet addresses the once-was object of his affection, and becomes reflective as he addresses the need to be joyful while still young."]}, "10": {"question": "Finzi - What does the text consist of?", "correct": "Two six-line stanzas or sextains", "incorrect": ["Three six-line stanzas or sextains", "Six four-line stanzas or quatrains", "Hobicore vibes"]}, "11": {"question": "What is the role of the piano in O Mistress Mine?", "correct": "It sets up the general feeling in the introduction and remains remarkably consistent in mood, supporting the vocal part.", "incorrect": ["It is accompanied by the vocal part"]}, "12": {"question": "Which play is the text of Let Us Garlands Bring from?", "correct": "Twelfth Night by Shakespeare", "incorrect": ["Twelfth Day by Shakespeare", "Ninth Night by Shakespeare", "Life Goes On by BTS"]}, "13": {"question": "Finzi - How is the vocal line?", "correct": "Simple and direct", "incorrect": ["Extravagant and indirect", "Excessively simple", "Straightfoward and monotonous"]}, "14": {"question": "Finzi - How is the text set?", "correct": "Syllabic and has a natural rhythm close to the declamation of the words.", "incorrect": ["Melismatic and has a rhythm not very close to the declamation of the words.", "Melismatic but has a natural rhythm close to the declamation of the words.", "Syllabic but has a rhythm not very close to the declamation of the words."]}, "15": {"question": "How does Finzi emphasise the point of the text?", "correct": "By using direct imitation between the voice and the piano at the final line of each stanza", "incorrect": ["By using direct imitation between the voice and the piano at the final line of the piece", "By using direct imitation between the voice and the piano of motifs throughout the piece", "By using direct imitation between the voice and the piano at the first line of each stanza"]}, "16": {"question": "Finzi - What key does the harmony shift to at the final line of each stanza?", "correct": "The parallel minor", "incorrect": ["The dominant", "The relative minor", "The parallel major"]}, "17": {"question": "Finzi - What is the form of the song?", "correct": "Semi-strophic", "incorrect": ["Modified strophic", "Simple strophic", "Binary"]}, "18": {"question": "Finzi - What are the stanzas framed by?", "correct": "A piano inroduction, interlude and postlude", "incorrect": ["A piano introduction, interlude and voice+piano postlude", "A voice+piano introduction, interlude and postlude", "A voice introduction, voice+piano interlude, voice postlude"]}, "19": {"question": "Finzi - What key is the piece in?", "correct": "E flat major", "incorrect": ["A flat major", "E major", "F major"]}, "20": {"question": "What key does O Mistress Mine modulate to?", "correct": "It does not modulate", "incorrect": ["C minor", "The parallel minor", "G minor"]}, "21": {"question": "Finzi - How is the melody written?", "correct": "Mostly diatonic except for the end of each stanza where a modal mixture is introduced", "incorrect": ["Mostly chromatic except for the end of each stanza where it becomes diatonic", "All diatonic", "Mostly diatonic except for the end of the piece where a modal mixture is introduced"]}, "22": {"question": "Finzi - What is the mood of the piece?", "correct": "Light-hearted and jaunty but becomes more reflective as modal mixture is introduced", "incorrect": ["Reflective but becomes more light-hearted and jaunty as modal mixture is introduced", "Light-hearted and jaunty", "Reflective"]}, "23": {"question": "Which syllables does Finzi ensure land on the first beat of the bar?", "correct": "Stressed", "incorrect": ["Unstressed", "Both", "jUst rAndOm syLLaBLeS"]}, "24": {"question": "Finzi - Where are the only instances of direct imitation found?", "correct": "At the end of each stanza between the voice and the piano", "incorrect": ["At the beginning of each stanza between the voice and the piano", "There are no instances of direct imitation in the piece", "At the end of the piece between the voice and the piano"]}, "25": {"question": "Finzi - Describe the texture of the accompaniment at the end of the each stanza.", "correct": "Legato articulation and longer note values, slower pace, and dramatic contrast of dynamics.", "incorrect": ["Staccato articulation and shorter note values, faster pace, no contrast of dynamics.", "Legato articulation and longer note values, slower pace, less contrast of dynamics.", "Legato articulation and shorter note values, slower pace and dramatic contrast of dynamics."]}, "26": {"question": "Finzi - Describe the cadence at the end of each stanza?", "correct": "It is joined with the commencement of the next piano section (interlude/postlude)", "incorrect": ["It is separated from the next piano section (interlude/postlude)", "It is joined with the commencement of the next stanza", "It is joined with a four-bar outro of sorts before the interlude/postlude commences"]}, "27": {"question": "Finzi - In what way is the piece flexible and natural?", "correct": "The voice sets the text differently in each stanza while the accompaniment stays the same.", "incorrect": ["The accompaniment is different in each stanza while the voice stays the same.", "The voice sets the text differently in each stanza, just like the accompaniment.", "The voice and accompaniment stay the same, but rubato and ornaments are used."]}, "28": {"question": "Generally, what is the role of the Piano in Art songs?", "correct": "Shares prominence with the vocal part", "incorrect": ["Secondary to the vocal part", "Ternary to the vocal part", "Primary above the vocal part", "Quaternary to the vocal part"]}, "29": {"question": "Let us garlands bring is a set of how many songs?", "correct": "Five", "incorrect": ["Thirteen", "Eight", "Eleven"]}, "30": {"question": "What does Allegretto amabile mean?", "correct": "Moderately fast and pleasant", "incorrect": ["Not too fast and pleasant", "Very fast and unpleasant", "Walking pace and pleasant"]}, "31": {"question": "Finzi - Which of the following is NOT a stylistic characteristic of the song?", "correct": "Use of raised 7th notes in minor keys", "incorrect": ["Some dissonance and occasional use of parallel 5ths to the bass", "Irregular phrase lengths and syncopation and changes of meter", "Angular melodies (at times)"]}, "32": {"question": "What does sempre staccato mean?", "correct": "Always detached", "incorrect": ["Never detached", "The Ravenswood magazine", "Very detached"]}, "33": {"question": "Finzi - What key is the piano part in?", "correct": "E flat major", "incorrect": ["E flat minor", "A major", "A minor"]}, "34": {"question": "Which of the following techniques does Finzi NOT use in the song?", "correct": "Chromatic harmony", "incorrect": ["Imitation", "Counterpoint", "Diatonic harmony"]}, "35": {"question": "What kind of techniques does Finzi deliberately use in the song?", "correct": "Techniques associated with earlier music styles from Shakespeare's time", "incorrect": ["Techniques ahead of Finzi's time", "Techniques associated with earlier styles such as Classical", "Techniques associated with Kpop"]}, "36": {"question": "Finzi - What is the underlying message of the song?", "correct": "To seize life's joys and pleasures while you can", "incorrect": ["To be yourself", "To pursue your dreams", "To listen to BTS"]}, "37": {"question": "Finzi - Which of the following is NOT part of the change in texture at the end of each stanza?", "correct": "Faster", "incorrect": ["Broader", "Denser", "Slower"]}, "38": {"question": "Finzi - Who is the piece sung by?", "correct": "Feste, the jester in the court of Countess Olivia", "incorrect": ["Countess Olivia, to her jester, Feste", "Feste, the brother of Countess Olivia", "Feste, the father of Countess Olivia"]}, "39": {"question": "Finzi: What kind of song is this?", "correct": "An English art song", "incorrect": ["A Lied", "A pop song", "An instrumental song", "A British art song"]}, "40": {"question": "Finzi: How far back does the genre English art song go?", "correct": "Late sixteenth to early seventeenth centuries", "incorrect": ["Late seventeenth to early eighteenth centuries", "Late sixteenth to early eighteenth centuries", "Late fifteenth to early sixteenth centuries", "Back in my day"]}, "41": {"question": "Finzi: Lute songs by which composers are notable from the late sixteenth to early seventeenth centuries?", "correct": "John Dowland and Thomas Campion", "incorrect": ["John Dowland and Henry Purcell", "Ralph Vaughan Williams and Henry Purcell", "Michael Jackson and Thomas Campion", "John Dowland and William Walton"]}, "42": {"question": "Finzi: Whose works marked a high point in seventeenth century English music across all genres?", "correct": "Henry Purcell", "incorrect": ["Ralph Vaughan Williams", "Thomas Campion", "Arnold Bax", "Barack Obama"]}, "43": {"question": "Finzi: How did foreign influences come to dominate the musical landscape in England?", "correct": "The importation of Italian opera and in the works of Handel", "incorrect": ["Uncontrolled immigration", "Work opportunities attracting foreigners to England", "Serious self-esteem issues on the part of English composers (most of which fell into a deep depression)", "Their music was more appealing to audiences in England"]}, "44": {"question": "Finzi: The solo songs in England were dominantly developing where?", "correct": "From outside of England", "incorrect": ["In England", "Oceania", "Asia", "The Americas"]}, "45": {"question": "Finzi: The German tradition of the Lied was a large influence on the English art song. Which composers were part of that genre?", "correct": "Franz Schubert, Robert Schumann, Felix Mendelssohn, Johannes Brahms", "incorrect": ["Robert Schumman, Johannes Brahms, Johann Sebastian Bach, Franz Schubert", "Felix Mendehlssohn, Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart, Johann Wolfgang Beethoven, Robert Schumann", "Franz Schubert, Roberto Schumann, Felix Mendelssohn, Johann's Bras", "Franz Schubert, Felix Mendelssohn, Johannes Brahms, William Shakespeare"]}, "46": {"question": "Finzi: What factors led to a period termed by some as the 'English musical Renaissance'?", "correct": "A growing sense of national awareness amongst English musicians, supported by a folk-song revival movement", "incorrect": ["A growing sense of national identity and confidence amongst musicians in England", "An increase in English composers in England at the time creating more music", "Foreign composers claiming to be English immigrating to England and composing masterpieces", "A growing sense of national awareness that encouraged people to write less music"]}, "47": {"question": "Finzi: What kinds of music were rediscovered in the 'English musical Renaissance'?", "correct": " 'Pre-Handelian' English music (court music) and British folk music", "incorrect": ["Jazz music, especially the elevator variety", "British folk music and renaissance music", "Renaissance music and 'Pre-Handelian' English music (court music)", "Pre-Bachian' English music and British folk music"]}, "48": {"question": "Finzi: Examples of twentieth century composers that were beneficiaries of the re-emergence of English music after foreign domination:", "correct": "Ralph Vaughan Williams, John Ireland, Arnold Bax, William Walton, Benjamin Britten", "incorrect": ["John Ireland, Benjamin Britten, Franz Schubert, Mark Walton, Arnold Bax", "William Walton, Ralph Vaughan Williams, Henry Purcell, Benjamin Britten, Arnold Bax", "Ralph Vaughan Williams, John Coltrane, Arnold Bax, Benjamin Britten, Miles Davis", "Ralph Vaughan Williams, John England, Arnold Bax, William Waton, Benjamin Britain"]}, "49": {"question": "Finzi: Examples of important English poets whose texts were set to music include:", "correct": "Shakespeare, Milton, Wordsworth, Coleridge, Hardy", "incorrect": ["Shakespeare, Dickens, Coleridge, Hardy, Wordsworth", "Keats, Milton, Shakespeare, Donne, Wordsworth", "Blake, Wordsworth, Hardy, Keats, Shakespeare", "John Lennon, Paul McCartney, Ringo Starr, George Harrison"]}, "50": {"question": "Finzi: What instrumentation is an art song comprised of?", "correct": "Solo voice and instrumental accompaniment", "incorrect": ["String orchestra and soloist", "Solo voice", "Solo instrument and instrumental accompaniment", "A chamber choir with a string quartet"]}, "51": {"question": "Finzi: How many short cycles of songs did Finzi compose?", "correct": "At least 8", "incorrect": ["8", "At least 24", "10", "16"]}, "52": {"question": "Finzi: From which English poet is Finzi's Let us garlands bring's text from?", "correct": "Shakespeare", "incorrect": ["Coleridge", "Hardy", "Milhouse", "Wordsworth"]}, "53": {"question": "Finzi: Which of Shakespeare's plays is O mistress mine from?", "correct": "Twelfth Night", "incorrect": ["Macbeth", "Romeo and Juliet", "A Midsummer Night's Dream", "Hamlet"]}, "54": {"question": "Finzi: How many six-line stanzas (sextains) are there in the text?", "correct": "2", "incorrect": ["4", "6", "17.3", "8"]}, "55": {"question": "Finzi: What kind of rhyme scheme do the sextains have?", "correct": "aabccb", "incorrect": ["abacad", "x", "ababab", "abcabc"]}, "56": {"question": "Finzi: How is the form of the song best described?", "correct": "Semi-strophic", "incorrect": ["Strophic", "Through-composed", "Sonata form", "Binary form"]}, "57": {"question": "Finzi: What happens to the cadence at the end of each stanza?", "correct": "It is elided with the commencement of the next piano section", "incorrect": ["It is replaced with a sequence that leads to the commencement of the next piano section", "It is an imperfect cadence which leads nicely to the next section", "It is repeated except changed so it becomes a 'second go'", "The performer forgets about it because they have a mental blank and can't remember how to play their instrument"]}, "58": {"question": "What is a strophic song?", "correct": "Each stanza is set to the same music", "incorrect": ["No substantial repitition of music for each stanza", "A song without words", "A song with a very repetitive melody", "A song with a very repetitive harmony"]}, "59": {"question": "What is a through-composed song?", "correct": "No substantial repitition of music for each stanza", "incorrect": ["Each stanza is set to the same music", "A song without words", "A very thoroughly composed piece of music", "A song that has little to no repitition in it"]}, "60": {"question": "What is a semi-strophic song?", "correct": "Between strophic and through-composed, bit of the same music but also different in each stanza", "incorrect": ["A shorter strophic song", "A song with motifs and ideas that seem to match each other but are not the same", "A song with a repetitive melody that sometimes introduces new ideas", "A song that has verses that are the same as each other"]}, "61": {"question": "Where would the music be the same usually in a semi-strophic song?", "correct": "At the beginning of each stanza, being the most logical way to express identity", "incorrect": ["At the end of each stanza, being the best way to finish", "In the middle of each stanza because that is where the listener feels secure and understands the music", "At the beginning of the first stanza and the end of the second stanza", "At the end of the first stanza and the beginning of the second stanza"]}, "62": {"question": "Finzi: Which other composers have used this same text from Twelfth Night?", "correct": "Thomas Morley, Sullivan, Vaughan Williams, Charles Villers Stanford, Margaret Sutherland", "incorrect": ["Thomas Morley, Charles Dickens, Vaughan Williams, Margaret Sutherland", "Donald Trump, Vaughan Williams, Charles Villers Stanford, Sullivan, Thomas Morley", "Vaughan Williams, Shakespeare, Sullivan, Thomas Morley, Rudy Giuliani, Margaret Sutherland", "Purcell, Sullivan, Margaret Sutherland, Finzi, Thomas Morley"]}, "63": {"question": "Finzi: What key is O mistress mine in?", "correct": "Eb major", "incorrect": ["Bb major", "E major", "C minor", "Db major"]}, "64": {"question": "Finzi: Does O mistress mine ever modulate to another key?", "correct": "No", "incorrect": ["Yes", "Yes, to all 7 billion of them", "Nothing is impossible if you put your mind to it", "Definitely"]}, "65": {"question": "Finzi: How can the mood throughout most of the song be described?", "correct": "Light-hearted and jaunty", "incorrect": ["Dysphoric and delusional", "Anxious and irritable", "Cheerful and bright", "Melancholic and reflective"]}, "66": {"question": "Finzi: O mistress mine is mostly diatonic except for where?", "correct": "The final bars of each stanza where modal mixture is introduced", "incorrect": ["The opening bars of each stanza where the ideas are being introduced", "The middle of each stanza", "The bridges between the stanzas", "China because they banned the import of diatonic"]}, "67": {"question": "Finzi: Where does the mood change to become more reflective?", "correct": "At the end of each stanza with the modal mixture", "incorrect": ["At the beginning of each stanza", "At the beginning and the end of each stanza", "When it nears the end of its life", "In the middle of each stanza to add an element of surprise"]}, "68": {"question": "Finzi: What does the right hand primarily consist of?", "correct": "A free, two-part texture with occasional thickening", "incorrect": ["A free, three-part texture with occasional thinning", "A free flowing melody that occasionally thickens", "A restricted, two-part texture with occasional thickening", "Five fingers and a palm"]}, "69": {"question": "Finzi: What does the left hand primarily consist of?", "correct": "A staccato 'vamping' accompaniment", "incorrect": ["A staccato unpredictable accompaniment", "Long sustained notes from the chords", "A walking bass line", "A free flowing countermelody"]}, "70": {"question": "Finzi: What is a consistent feature present in the left hand accompaniment?", "correct": "A downward stepping motion from the second beat of the bar to the first beat of next bar", "incorrect": ["An upward stepping motion from the second beat of the bar to the first beat of the next bar", "A downward stepping motion from the first to the second beat of the bar", "Dominant tenths", "An upward stepping motion from the first to the second beat of the bar"]}, "71": {"question": "Finzi: How do the interlude and hte postlude compare to the introduction?", "correct": "They are quite similar", "incorrect": ["They substantially differ as they share no common music", "They are identical", "They are not related to each other in any way", "They are much shorter, but make up for it in dynamics"]}, "72": {"question": "Finzi: Are the musical material from the vocal line and the piano part dependent on each other?", "correct": "No they are relatively independent", "incorrect": ["Yes because they constantly imitate each other", "Yes due to how the parts interlock and play together", "No but they do share a lot of the same ideas, so actually yes", "Yes because they are both in a sticky financial situation due to the Coronavirus pandemic"]}, "73": {"question": "Finzi: What type of text setting is the text?", "correct": "Syllabic", "incorrect": ["Neumatic", "Melismatic", "Problematic", "Dolichocephalic"]}, "74": {"question": "Finzi: What is accountable for the subtle rhythm changes from stanza to stanza?", "correct": "Natural declamation", "incorrect": ["Rubato", "Natural tempo variation", "Natural emphasisation", "The incapable musician not being able to tap their foot"]}, "75": {"question": "Finzi: How do the first lines of each stanza compare rhythmically?", "correct": "Different in their natural speech rhythms and have a different number of syllables", "incorrect": ["They are the same", "They share some rhythmic groupings", "Different number of syllables but similar speech rhythms", "Different in their natural speech rhythms but same number of syllables"]}, "76": {"question": "Finzi: How does the piano accompaniment for the first lines of each stanza compare?", "correct": "It is identical", "incorrect": ["They are in different keys", "They are at different tempos", "They are similar with a few note changes", "The piano isn't playing at that part, get pranked Laugh Out LOUD"]}, "77": {"question": "Finzi: Does the highly flexible, natural text setting remain consistent throughout the song?", "correct": "Yes", "incorrect": ["No", "Maybe", "Possibly", "Naaaaaaaaaaah"]}, "78": {"question": "Finzi: At what points in the stanzas are the piano accompaniment and the melody similar?", "correct": "At the beginning and nearing the end", "incorrect": ["In the middle of both stanzas", "In the final line of both stanzas", "At the beginning of both stanzas", "Nowhere, because its a circle"]}, "79": {"question": "Finzi: Where is the only instance of direct imitation between the voice and the piano found?", "correct": "At the very final line in each stanza", "incorrect": ["The first line of each stanza", "The middle of the second stanza", "At the end of the song", "The beginning of the final stanza"]}, "80": {"question": "Finzi: What changes occur in the final two lines in each stanza?", "correct": "Harmony shifts to parallel minor, accompaniment texture changes, pace slows, dramatic dynamic contrast", "incorrect": ["Harmony shifts to parallel minor, pace quickens, overall texture becomes more dense and dynamics increase", "Harmony shifts up a major fifth, pace slows, accompaniment texture changes, dynamic contrast", "Pace quickens, accompaniment texture thins, pace slows, dynamics dramatically softer", "Nothing is changed here"]}}